{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947201759174","data":{"timestamp":" 947201759174"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000107_023546"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947201768491","data":{"timestamp":" 947201768491"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000107_023546"," gameId":" 2890ff72-00e5-4de9-97ea-750f969ad71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947201768722","data":{"timestamp":" 947201768721"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000107_023546"," gameId":" 2890ff72-00e5-4de9-97ea-750f969ad71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947201769693","data":{"timestamp":" 947201769693"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000107_023546"," gameId":" 2890ff72-00e5-4de9-97ea-750f969ad71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947201770969","data":{"timestamp":" 947201770969"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000107_023546"," gameId":" 2890ff72-00e5-4de9-97ea-750f969ad71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947201773848","data":{"timestamp":" 947201773847"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000107_023546"," gameId":" 2890ff72-00e5-4de9-97ea-750f969ad71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947201774691","data":{"timestamp":" 947201774691"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000107_023546"," gameId":" 2890ff72-00e5-4de9-97ea-750f969ad71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947201775004","data":{"timestamp":" 947201775004"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000107_023546"," gameId":" 2890ff72-00e5-4de9-97ea-750f969ad71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947201776237","data":{"timestamp":" 947201776237"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000107_023546"," gameId":" 2890ff72-00e5-4de9-97ea-750f969ad71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947201779768","data":{"timestamp":" 947201779768"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000107_023546"," gameId":" 2890ff72-00e5-4de9-97ea-750f969ad71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947201780762","data":{"timestamp":" 947201780762"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000107_023546"," gameId":" 2890ff72-00e5-4de9-97ea-750f969ad71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947201781024","data":{"timestamp":" 947201781024"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000107_023546"," gameId":" 2890ff72-00e5-4de9-97ea-750f969ad71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947201781973","data":{"timestamp":" 947201781972"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000107_023546"," gameId":" 2890ff72-00e5-4de9-97ea-750f969ad71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947201784900","data":{"timestamp":" 947201784900"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000107_023546"," gameId":" 2890ff72-00e5-4de9-97ea-750f969ad71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947201785933","data":{"timestamp":" 947201785933"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000107_023546"," gameId":" 2890ff72-00e5-4de9-97ea-750f969ad71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947201786405","data":{"timestamp":" 947201786405"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000107_023546"," gameId":" 2890ff72-00e5-4de9-97ea-750f969ad71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947201790956","data":{"timestamp":" 947201790955"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000107_023546"," gameId":" 2890ff72-00e5-4de9-97ea-750f969ad71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947201791022","data":{"timestamp":" 947201791022"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000107_023546"," gameId":" 2890ff72-00e5-4de9-97ea-750f969ad71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947201804297","data":{"timestamp":" 947201804297"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000107_023546"," gameId":" 2890ff72-00e5-4de9-97ea-750f969ad71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947201816583","data":{"timestamp":" 947201816583"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000107_023546"," gameId":" e7d2dcaa-01f9-499f-bcab-fd12091f3bf6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_11-14-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947201823397","data":{"timestamp":" 947201823397"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000107_023546"," gameId":" e7d2dcaa-01f9-499f-bcab-fd12091f3bf6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-12-7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947201829425","data":{"timestamp":" 947201829425"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000107_023546"," gameId":" e7d2dcaa-01f9-499f-bcab-fd12091f3bf6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_3-10-11"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947201834929","data":{"timestamp":" 947201834929"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000107_023546"," gameId":" e7d2dcaa-01f9-499f-bcab-fd12091f3bf6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_8-12-7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947201871313","data":{"timestamp":" 947201871313"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000107_023546"," gameId":" 15a8076d-4a3f-4fe5-94d5-1d7c4d3f3cee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_10-14-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947201901142","data":{"timestamp":" 947201901142"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000107_023546"," gameId":" 1da0006c-56ec-479d-adab-6fe3e8d439e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_3-13-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947201905746","data":{"timestamp":" 947201905746"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000107_023546"," gameId":" 1da0006c-56ec-479d-adab-6fe3e8d439e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_9-11-4"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947201911864","data":{"timestamp":" 947201911864"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000107_023546"," gameId":" 1da0006c-56ec-479d-adab-6fe3e8d439e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_9-11-4"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947201918401","data":{"timestamp":" 947201918400"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000107_023546"," gameId":" 1da0006c-56ec-479d-adab-6fe3e8d439e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_9-11-4"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947201924484","data":{"timestamp":" 947201924484"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000107_023546"," gameId":" 1da0006c-56ec-479d-adab-6fe3e8d439e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_12_10-3-12"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 12"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947201930142","data":{"timestamp":" 947201930142"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000107_023546"," gameId":" 1da0006c-56ec-479d-adab-6fe3e8d439e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_12_10-3-12"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 12"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947201938324","data":{"timestamp":" 947201938324"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000107_023546"," gameId":" 1da0006c-56ec-479d-adab-6fe3e8d439e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_9-11-4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947201945263","data":{"timestamp":" 947201945263"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000107_023546"," gameId":" 1da0006c-56ec-479d-adab-6fe3e8d439e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_12_12-6-7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 12"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947201952418","data":{"timestamp":" 947201952418"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000107_023546"," gameId":" 1da0006c-56ec-479d-adab-6fe3e8d439e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_12_12-6-7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 12"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947201959781","data":{"timestamp":" 947201959781"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000107_023546"," gameId":" 1da0006c-56ec-479d-adab-6fe3e8d439e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_10-11-6"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947201966298","data":{"timestamp":" 947201966298"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000107_023546"," gameId":" 1da0006c-56ec-479d-adab-6fe3e8d439e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_12-14-7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947201973958","data":{"timestamp":" 947201973957"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000107_023546"," gameId":" 1da0006c-56ec-479d-adab-6fe3e8d439e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_9-11-4"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947201979443","data":{"timestamp":" 947201979443"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000107_023546"," gameId":" 1da0006c-56ec-479d-adab-6fe3e8d439e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_10-14-7"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947201985753","data":{"timestamp":" 947201985753"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000107_023546"," gameId":" 1da0006c-56ec-479d-adab-6fe3e8d439e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_10-14-7"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947201992067","data":{"timestamp":" 947201992067"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000107_023546"," gameId":" 1da0006c-56ec-479d-adab-6fe3e8d439e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_12_8-12-7"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 12"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947201999123","data":{"timestamp":" 947201999123"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000107_023546"," gameId":" 1da0006c-56ec-479d-adab-6fe3e8d439e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_12_8-12-7"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}